tech21century.com 2017-07-10

# Privacy-Disclaimer | Tech 21 Century

## PRIVACY POLICY

At **tech21century.com** we are dedicated to safeguarding and preserving your privacy when visiting our site or communicating electronically with us. This Privacy Policy provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you.

We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.

**Information We Collect**

In operating our website we may collect and process the following data about you:

i.            Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data.

ii.            Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website, such as when you registered for information or make a purchase.

iii.            Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.

**Use of Cookies**

On occasion, we may gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website to our advertisers.

Such information will not identify you personally it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever. ****

Similarly to the above, we may gather information about your general internet use by using a cookie file.  Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you.

All computers have the ability to decline cookies.  This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website.

Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.  Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.

**Use of Your Information**

The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used for statistical purposes and will NEVER be sold or given away to anyone else.

Please be advised that we do not reveal information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate statistical information about our visitors.

**Third Party Links**

You mind find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.

**DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Google Adsense**

Google AdSense ads run in various places in this website. Please visit Google Adsense to review their [privacy policies](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Given the nature of Google’s service, it is not possible for us to review and approve advertisers and vendors or their products and services.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Contacting Us**

We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy.  Please do not hesitate to contact us using the CONTACT page on our website.

## DISCLAIMER

We are not responsible for any data loss or damage that might be caused by the information, suggestions, guides, problem solutions etc provided herein. Also product selection and use are up to you.

The information services and resources provided in this website are based upon the current Internet environment as well as the website owner’s experience. The techniques presented here have been proven to be successful. Because technologies are constantly changing, the services and examples presented in this website may change, cease or expand with time. We hope that the skills and knowledge acquired from this website will provide you with the ability to adapt to inevitable evolution of technological services. However, we cannot be held responsible for changes that may affect the applicability of these techniques. The opinions expressed in this website belong to the website owner and are not necessarily those of Cisco Systems, Inc. All product names, logos and artwork are copyrights of their respective owners. None of the owners have sponsored or endorsed this website. While all attempts have been made to verify information provided, the author assumes no responsibility for errors, omissions, or contrary interpretation of the subject matter herein. Any perceived slights of peoples or organizations are unintentional. Visitors and readers of this website assume responsibility for the use of these materials and information. No guarantees of income are made. The website owner assumes no responsibility or liability whatsoever on behalf of any reader of the content in this website.

This website (www.tech21century.com) entails my own thoughts and ideas, which may not represent the thoughts of Cisco Systems Inc. This website is not affiliated with Cisco Systems Inc.

All brand names and product names used herein, are trade names, service marks, trademarks, or registered trademarks of their respective owners. The website owner is not associated with any product or vendor mentioned, including Cisco Systems. PIX and ASA Firewalls are registered trademarks of Cisco Systems, Inc..

**Disclosure** : You should assume that the owner of this website is an affiliate for providers of goods, products and services mentioned on this website. The owner may be compensated when you purchase after clicking on a link. The owner may also have received the product for free. Perform due diligence before purchasing from this or any other website.
